Ми ж все одно програємо.
We're going to lose anyway.
Отані.
Otani.
Дурень!
You idiot!
Ти ледащо!
You slacker!
O T A N I
D o  y o u r b e s t !
D o  y o u r b es t !
O T A N I
D o  y our best!
Уперед!
Do your best!
Мабуть, мені просто погано без тебе, Коїзумі.
I guess I'm just... no good without you, Koizumi.
Найкращий день народження.
The Best Birthday in History
Мені погано без тебе, Коїзумі.
I'm just no good without you, Koizumi.
Отані...
Otani...
Завтра починаються літні канікули.
And so, summer vacation starts tomorrow.
Припини!
Stop that!
Годі...
Me too...
Коїзумі!
Koizumi-san!
Які плани?
What are you going to do over the summer vacation?
Ну...
Hmm...Well...
Прекрасний сон.
What a nice dream.
Літо. Останнє шкільне літо.
Summer. The last summer of my high school life.
Я досі не знаю почуття Отані, але...
I still don't know how Otani feels, but...
Я повеселюся!
I'm gonna have some fun!
Запис на літні заняття
Summer Studies Sign up
Ти забула, що скоро вступні іспити?
You lot have forgotten that you'll be sitting entrance exams soon, haven't you?
Так. Повністю.
Yes. I completely forgot.
Для тих дурбеликів, кого я назвав, літні заняття є обов'язковими.
For the little idiots I just named, the summer study session is compulsory.
напис дурбелик
Little        Idiot
Вам доведеться багато працювати, щоб компенсувати минулі лінощі.
You have to work hard to make up for your past laziness.
Ясно?
Got it?
У вас не буде канікул.
You exam students don't get a vacation.
Ні...
No...
Моє миле літечко...
My precious summer...
Виходить,
So in the end,
лише Чіхару та Сузукі не займатимуться улітку.
Chiharu-chan and Suzuki-kun are the only ones who don't need to attend summer classes...
Це все через побачення у бібліотеці.
That's because they have study dates at the library every day.
Ми справді вчилися разом.
They're not dates. We just study.
Але ми теж ходитимемо.
But we'll be attending summer classes too.
А я думала, що матиму нагоду повеселитися.
And here I thought I'd have the chance to have loads of fun...
Які ще веселощі?!
What do you mean loads of fun?!
Ти дурепа, що постійно проґавлює вдалі моменти, засинає і нічого не чує!
An idiot like you who misses all the important stuff, sleeping away and not hearing the best part!!!
Та що ти як з ланцюга зірвалася?!
What's got you so angry these days?!
Знову літні заняття?
So we've got to attend summer classes again this year?
І тепер я можу розважитися, коли пішов з клубу.
And here I thought I could have fun, now that I'm done with basketball club.
Я думав ти пішов, щоб більше вчитися.
I thought you retired so that you could concentrate on your studies?
Ну так...
Oh well...
Що ж, зате мені не потрібний привід, щоб бачитись з Отані улітку
Well, at least I don't need to come up with any excuses to hang out with Otani over the summer,
це добре.
I guess it's not so bad.
Нобу, а чому ти не займалась з Накао?
Nobu-chan, why didn't you plan study dates with Nakao-chi too?
Не двієчниці мене питати.
I don't see why the ones with red crosses all over her work should be asking me that.
Спека...Ну й спека...
Hot... So hot...
Ти танеш?!
Why are you melting?!
Я не можу...
I can't take it...
Хочете освіжитись?
Want to go somewhere cool?
Так!
Yes~!
Ура! Рай!
Yay! Paradise!
Я жива!
I'm revived!
Що замовлятимете?
What would you like to order?
А так, так, замовлення...
Oh yes, yes, My order...
Подивимось...
Let's see...
Новий напій?
Oh! A new item on the menu?
Я хочу його.
I'm gonna try it.
Один Полінезійський Танцювальник!
One Polynesian Dancer!
Чого повторюєш?
Why are you copying me?
Це ти повторюєш.
You're the one who's copying me.
Напій дня.
I'll go with the drink bar.
Мені теж.
Me too.
І мені.
Same here.
Me too.
Дякую. Один момент.
Thank you. Please wait one moment.
Чіхару, яке миле кільце.
Chiharu-chan, that's a cute ring.
Дякую.
Uh, thank you.
Звідки воно?
When did you get that?
Ну...
Eh? Well...
Це Сузукі тобі подарував?
Oh? Did Suzuki-kun give it to you?
У тебе ж нещодавно був день народження?
It was your birthday not long ago, wasn't it?
А...так.
Uh...yes.
А. Добре.
Ah. Well done.
Молодець, Сузукі.
Well done, Suzuki-chi.
Так... Мабуть...
Uh... I guess...
Нобу, тобі теж щось подарували на день народження?
Oh, Nobu-chan, you got something for your birthday too, didn't you?
Так. Сумочку!
Yeah. A handbag!
Вибач, що найдешевшу.
Sorry it was only a cheap one.
Нічого.
It's okay.
Головне, що з любов'ю.
It was given with love, after all.
Люблю тебе, Нобу.
I love you Nobu-chan~
І я тебе! Люблю-люблю-люблю.
Me too! I love love love you~
І я лю-лю-лю-лю-лю-лю-люблю!
I love love love love love love love you~
Люблю!
I love you~
Які усі щасливі.
Everyone's happy, huh...
Я згадала! Скоро день народження Ріси.
Oh! that reminds me, it's almost Risa's birthday!
хе... хе... хе... хе...
smirk... smirk... smirk... smirk...
Що? Що з вами?!
Hey! What's up with this atmosphere?!
Отані, ти ж приготуєш подарунок для Коїзумі?
Otani-chi, naturally you'll be giving Koizumi-san a present, won't you?
Так.
Yeah.
Він же не може жити без Коїзумі, так?
I mean, he just can't live without Koizumi-san, right?
Що це було? Пропозиція?
What was that anyway? A proposal?
Якого біса? Ви підслуховували?
Wha-What the hell?! You guys were listening?!
Ми все чули.
We heard it all.
Що?
What?
Я не казав, що не можу жити без неї!
I didn't say I couldn't live without her!
Про що ви?
What's this about?
Заціпся! Не твоє діло!
Shut up! It's none of your business!
Агов! Що коїться?! Це мене дратує!
Hey! What's going on?! This is getting on my nerves!
Замовкни! Сиди тихо!
Shut up! Just be quiet!
Один Полінезійський...
For the customer who ordered the Polynesian Dancer...
Нарешті! Мій Полінезійський!
Oh, it's here! My Polynesian Dancer!
Полінезійський....
Mmmmm... Polynesian....
Ми не про це.
That's not the point.
Та що таке?
What the heck?
Коїзумі!
Koizumi!
Привіт.
Hey.
Боже! Я зрозумів!
Geez! I get it!
Що ти хочеш?
What do you want?
Що ти хочеш на день народження?
What do you want for your birthday?
Нічого.
I don't want anything.
Вередуєш мною?
Are you refusing my good intentions?
Може краще розкажеш про учора?
More importantly, what were you talking about yesterday?
Просто забудь про це.
Th-That was... just forget about it.
Як я можу?
How can I?
Всі лише дивно відмовчуються.
No one is telling me anything, and everyone seems to find it hilarious.
Дратує!
It's really irritating me!
Забудь те і скажи, чого хочеш.
Forget it, okay. Just tell me what you want.
Нічого, я ж кажу.
Nothing. I don't want anything.
Правда?
Seriously?
Не скаржся мені потім, якщо я тобі нічого не подарую.
Don't complaint to me later if I don't give you anything.
Я сказала, що нічого не хочу!
I told you I don't want anything!
Ну чому ти завжди все псуєш?!
Why do you always make things worse?!
Та я ненавмисне...
Well, I just unconsciously...
Дурепа!
Idiot!
Але!..
But...!
Але так і є!
But it's true!
Я не хочу миле колечко чи сумочку.
I don't want a cute ring or a handbag.
Єдине чого я хочу...
The only thing I want is...
кохання Отані!
...Otani's love!
Не торкайся мене!
Get away from me!
Я удома.
I'm home.
Як спекотно.
Yeesh, It's so hot...
Який вітерець.
Ahh. What a nice wind.
День народження?
My birthday, huh?
Згадається минулий рік.
Come to think of it, on my birthday last year...
Я люблю тебе, Отані!
I like you, Otani!
Що з тобою? Сказонеш ще таке...
What's with you? Saying a thing like that out of nowhere...
Ти мене соромиш.
You're embarrassing me.
Мене не сприйняли серйозно, але...
Well, I wasn't taken seriously, but...
Утім, пройшов уже рік, еге ж?
It's been a whole year since then, huh?
Умібозу!
Umibouzu!
Можливо, мені підходить така, як ти.
Maybe someone like you is more suited to me.
Що ти сказав?
What did you say?
Думки вголос.
Just talking to myself.
Я дурепа.
I'm a real idiot.
Прийми це!
Accept it!
Коїзумі...
Ko-Koizumi...
Koizumi...
Досить.
I've had enough.
Досить з мене.
I've had enough of this.
Я тебе більше не люблю!
I'm through with loving you!
Багато чого сталося, але... Цікаво, чи окупились мої старання?
A lot has happened, but... I wonder if my hard work has paid off?
Він же не може жити без Коїзумі, так?
I mean, he just can't live without Koizumi-san, right?
Я не казав, що не можу жити без неї!
I never said I can't live without her!
Про що це вони?
What were they talking about?
Якщо будеш щось купляти - поквапся.
If you're going to buy something, hurry up and do it.
Ми якось тут не вписуємося.
We're kind of out of place here.
Вона буде рада будь-чому від тебе.
I think she'll be happy with anything you get her.
Ні. Я не буду.
I'm not doing it. I'm not buying anything.
Це тупо. І неправильно.
This is stupid. It feels wrong.
Га? Не будеш?
Huh? You're not?
Тільки не даруй знову щось Умібозівське, це нудно.
Don't give her Umibouzu stuff again. That's boring.
Чому я маю прислухатись тебе?
Why should your boredom be my concern?
Сподіваюсь, на день народження станеться щось гарне.
I hope something good happens on my birthday this year.
Рісо.
Risa.
Подруго!
Senpai!
Га!
Ah!
Ти теж на заняттях, Харуко?
You have to attend summer classes too, Haruka?
Ні. Хотів побачитись.
Nope. I just wanted to see you.
Хоча Харука на вигляд не розумний,
Haruka-senpai may not look very smart,
але він гарно вчиться.
but he's quick to understand things so he does well on tests.
Сейко...
Seiko-chin...
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Це тобі, Коїзумі.
Here, Koizumi-senpai.
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Koizumi Risa
Birthday Party
Invitation
August 3rd is Risa's
Birthday
Lets all enjoy it together
Place: Home Ec Room
Time: 5PM
Га? Що це?
Huh? What's this?
Запрошення на день народження Коїзумі Ріси?
An invitation to Koizumi Risa's Birthday Party?
Так. Ми збираємось приготувати багато смачної їжі та торт!
Yeah. We're going to prepare lots of delicious food and cake and host it!
Клич усіх!
Invite everyone, okay!
Ви такі милі, народе!
Y-You guys are so nice!
Я такий. Люби ме.
I am, huh. Feel free to fall for me.
Ніколи.
Not gonna happen.
Жорстока!
How cruel!
Забудь. Я завоюю тебе своїми навичками господаря.
Forget it. I'll just win you over with my party hosting skills.
Отаніi!
Otani-senpai!
Ось. Тримай.
Here. Take one.
Що це?
What's this?
Запрошення на вечірку Коїзумі.
An invitation to Koizumi-senpai's birthday party.
Приходь!
Please come, okay?
Коїзумі?
For Koizumi's birthday?
У мене немає вибору.
I'm inviting you because I don't have a choice.
Краще так, ніж ви двоє будете десь удвох насамоті.
Better this that having you two off alone somewhere.
Харуко! Невже у тебе справді такий мотив?
Haruka-senpai! Did you really have such an underhanded motive?
Кажи що хочеш.
Say what you want.
Ріса не дістанеться лише тобі на своєму святі.
I'm not going to let you have Risa all to yourself on her birthday.
Ти злодій!
You're the worst!
Я теж хочу святкувати з нею.
Well, I want to celebrate with her too.
Накао та Нобу теж прийдуть на вечірку?
Nakao and Nobu-chan are both planning to go to your party, huh?
Вчитель Майті також.
Maity-sensei is going to come too.
А ти, Отані?
What about you, Otani?
Прийдеш?
Are you going to come?
Я думав, ти не хочеш.
I though you didn't want me to do anything for your birthday?
І від подарунка відмовилась.
You said you didn't want a present from me.
Я не мала це на увазі!
I-I didn't mean it like that!
А що?
Then what did you mean?
Що значить "не можеш жити без мене"?
Then what does "Can't live without me" mean?
Я сказав, що не казав цього. І не сказав би!
I-I said I didn't say that! as if I'd say that!
Ти про що?
What's this all about?
Я тоді спала?
Did this happen when I fell asleep that time?
Вони не так зрозуміли!
I-I told you, they got it all wrong!
Я точно їх передушу.
Man, I'm seriously going to get those guys.
Гей, а вечірка?
Hey, What about the party?
А мені що!
Like I care!
Отані!
Otani!
Що за хрінь?!
What the heck?!
Вибачте, я...
Sorry I'm late!
З днем народження, з днем народження
Happy Birthday to you, Happy Birthday to you,
З днем народження, Рісо
Happy Birthday dear Risa...
Я така щаслива...
I..I'm so happy...
З днем народження!
Happy Birthday to you!
Вітаємо, Рісо!
Congratulations, Risa!
Дякую, дякую.
Thank you, thank you.
Ти довго говорила з керівником.
You sure had a long talk with our homeroom teacher.
Чого він хотів?
What did he call you for?
Говорили за мої двійки...
Well, my test results were pretty terrible...
А де Отані?
Huh? Where's Otani-kun?
Він не тут?
He's not here?
Ні.
Nope.
Ми думали, ви разом.
We thought he was with you.
А вечірка?
Hey, what about the party?
А мені що!
Like I care!
Мабуть, він удома.
Well, maybe he went home.
Ну і фіг з ним.
Who cares if he's not here.
Давай, Рісо.
Come on, Risa.
Харуко...
Haruka-senpai....
це твоїх рук діло?!
...don't tell me this is your doing?!
Я нічого не робив!
I didn't do a thing!
О ні! Така реакція дуже підозріла.
Oh no! This aggressive reaction is very suspicious.
Ах ти...
You...
Ааа! Стає ще гірше.
Ahhh! he's getting worse!
Припини це!
Stop this ridiculousness!
Поставте десь.
Now, now. Let's put that aside.
"Поставте десь"?
"Put that aside"?
Вітаю тебе, Коїзумі.
Happy Birthday, Koizumi-san.
Вчителю Майті!
Maity-sensei!
Вітаю.
Congratulations.
Щиро вдячна!
Thank you so much!
Присядь.
Now, take a seat.
Ти почесний гість.
You're the guest of honor today.
Справді, я вклав у ці страви всю свою любов для тебе, Рісо.
That's right! I just put all of my love for you into this food, just to make you happy, Risa.
Ого! А пахне яяяяк!
Wow! It smells so good!
Я голодна!
I'm so hungry!
Зажди, Рісо. А Отані?
Wait Risa. What about Otani-kun?
Ого! Цей торт такий милий!
Wow! This cake is super cute!
Справді? Я сама прикрашала.
Isn't it? Isn't it? I decorated it myself.
А подивись на це!
Never mind that. Check this out!
Я приготував твоє улюблене: Чірашізуші, смажену курку, сендвічі, такоякі, картоплю фрі
I made all your favorites: Chirashizushi, fried chicken, sandwiches, takoyaki, French fries,
та пасту Неаполітано!
and spaghetti with Neapolitan sauce!
Боже!
Geez!
Не відповідає. Куди подівся Отані?
He's not answering his phone. Where could Otani have gone?
Що коїться! Я шаленію!
What's going on! This is so frustrating!
Вони точно подобаються один одному, але...
They're definitely both interested in each other now...
Це точно!
That's true!
Все добре.
It's fine.
Навіть якщо Отані не прийшов, усі інші зі мною.
Even if Otani isn't around, everyone else is here celebrating with me.
Це була смакота!
Ahh. That was just delicious!
Я радий!
You're very welcome.
Ви чуєте щось з вулиці?
Hey, did you hear something from outside?
Так. Феєрверки, мабуть.
Yeah. It's probably fireworks.
Точно, сьогодні фестиваль.
Oh yeah. I heard there's a fireworks festival on today.
Справді?
Really?
Ми можемо подивитись з даху.
If we go up to the roof, we should be able to see them.
Феєрверки?
Fireworks?
Як минулого року...
Come to think of it, last year too...
Рісо, ходімо на дах.
Risa, let's go up to the roof.
Я бачу їх! Бачу!
Ah! I can see them! I can see them!
Гарно!
How pretty!
Красиво...
Beautiful...
Круто!
Amazing!
Вау!
Wow!
Думав тебе розрадить.
I thought watching the fireworks would cheer you up.
Ого. Які вони гарні.
Wow. They sure are pretty.
Це недобре.
It really is no good.
Без Отані поруч феєрверки мені не подобаються
If Otani's not with me, I just don't find the fireworks pretty...
і не радують.
...and I can't cheer up.
Пес майонез, тобі СМС.
Yo, this is for real. You got mail.
СМС?
Mail?
Отані
Озирнися
Otani
Behind You
Що це?
What's this?
Те що не хотіла.
Something you didn't want.
Подарунок.
A present.
Та ти що!
Huh? No way!
А я брехатиму?
Why would I lie?
Я можу відкрити? Я вже почала.
Can I open it? I've already opened it, thought....
Це не у моєму стилі, але в тебе усе у кролях, тож я...
It's not my style, but you always have rabbit stuff, so I just went and...
Ого! Це супер мило!
Wow! It's super cute!
Сховай. Вони нас помітять.
Keep it down! They'll see us.
Боляче.
That hurt!
Що це?
What's that?
Феєрверки. Купив поруч.
Fireworks. I bought them at the convenience store.
Круто. Покличмо інших і...
Cool. Then let's get everyone and...
Зачекай. Заховай це зараз.
You can do that later. Just put that away for now.
Це?
This?
Якщо вони побачать, то потім життя мені не дадуть, розумієш.
If they find out I bought you that, they won't let me live it down, you know?
Ти спізнився через подарунок?
Don't tell me you were late because you went to buy this?
Де він був?
Where did you get it?
Яка різниця?
Does it matter where?
Дякую. Мені приємно.
Thanks. I'm really happy.
Справді?
Really?
Я думала, ти не прийдеш.
I thought you weren't going to come.
Думала, що мені не добре без Отані.
I was just thinking "I guess I'm just not good without Otani".
Ти слухаєш?
Hey, are you listening?
Слухаю.
I'm listening.
Я сказав те саме після того матчу.
I said the same thing after that last basketball match.
Хоча дехто не чув, бо відрубався.
Although someone fell asleep and didn't hear me.
Мабуть, мені просто погано без тебе, Коїзумі.
I guess I'm just... no good without you, Koizumi.
Тож, це був не сон...
So... that wasn't a dream...
Коїзумі...
Koizumi...
Зроби інший вираз, прошу
Can't you pull a better face than that?
Що? Але, ее
What? But... uh...
В тебе знову гарячка?
Do you have a fever again?
Це не так.
It's not like that.
А... Це не так... Це не так...
Ah... Not like that... Not like that...
Не смійся.
Don't laugh.
А... що тоді це?
Then... what is this?
Я досі сплю?
Am I still dreaming?
Чи це не сон?
This isn't a dream, right?
Перше побачення з Отані!
My first date with Otani!
Отані приніс це для мене!
Otani bought it for me - !
Ти спізнилася!
You're late!
Купиш мені за це сік.
Why don't you buy me juice as penance?
Я забула гаманець.
Oh! I forgot my purse...
Дурепа!
You idiot!
Зворушливий комплекс. Звор ком.
Lovely Complex~ Love Com.
Далі: Перше побачення - перші проблеми!
Next: Sudden Downturn!! The First Date is the Beginning of Misfortune
Перше побачення - перші проблеми!
Sudden Downturn!! The First Date is the Beginning of Misfortune
Не пропустіть!
Be sure to watch!